--------ED------------
Another earthquake?
また地震
We've getting many recentl—
このところ多いね
Who's there?!
何方　私を常盤台の婚后光子と知っての狼
How dare you do something so horrible to Kongou Mitsuko from Tokiwadai?!
NOOOOOOO!
いやぁぁぁ
I hear there was another earthquake yesterday.
昨日もあったらしいねぇ　地震
How was your dormitory?
君の寮はどうだった
It was all right.
大丈夫です　うちのほうは揺れませんでした
It didn't shake at my place.
It's strange even though it's within the same 7th Academy District.
同じ第七学区なのに不思議だよねぇ
大圄先生　それで　あの　今日は
Daigo-sensei... Umm... Why am I here today?
Oh right.
はぁ　そう　そう
Come in.
入っておいで
She's a new transfer student coming in for the second trimester.
二学期からの転入生だ
She will also be your roommate from now on.
そして　これから君のルームメイトになる
I apologize for the short notice but, as you're the Judgement representative for our school,
急ですまないが
<Judgement>
我が校の風紀委員として
I would like you to be of assistance to her.
彼女の力になってほしいんだ
A-Absolutely!
はい　任せてください
Please leave everything to me!
My name is Haruue Erii.
春上　衿衣なの
響き合う願いが今覚醒めてく
脑海中回响着的愿望现已苏醒
譲れない未来のために
为了绝不可相让的未来
巡り逢う運命を超えたその先に
只因在超越命运的前方
この想い輝くから
这份思念正闪耀着光芒
ここじゃない未来に
在那并非归属的未来
想い託してみては
寄存着这份思念
強さの本当の意味を
继续寻找着那
搜し続けてた
强大的真正意义
ありのままの痛みを
将各种痛苦
受け入れるその意味を
全部承受的意义
明日へ走り続ける君に知った
是奔向明天的你告诉了我
巡りゆく景色が今流れてく
那眼前的景色现已过去
手繰り寄せた世界の先
那紧牵着双手的世界的前方
降り注ぐシグナルを躰で感じて
身体已感觉到其中所倾注的信号
解き放つ今全てを
此刻解放所有一切
Just truthin my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
无论何时都不应迷茫
消せない想いがあるから
因为有着无法磨灭的思念
解き明かす真実から瞳を逸らさずに
直视那已经揭开的真相
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
確かな絆信じて
请相信这份羁绊
A transfer student from the 19th Academy District.
第十九学区からの転入生か
But isn't it rare for her to come at this time of year?
でもこの時期に珍しくない
I would imagine they would normally try to time it at the start of the trimester.
普通は新学期の始まりに会わせそうなものですのにね
Oh hey Saten-san, you seem needlessly happy.
で　佐天さん　やけに嬉しそうですわね
Oh of course I am!
そりゃそうですよ
If she's Uiharu's roommate, she's my best friend candidate!
初春のルームメイトってことは　あたしの親友候補です
佐天さん
Saten-san!
Huh?
Umm...
えっと　春上衿衣さんです
This is Haruue Erii-san.
And this is...
で　こちらが　常盤台中学の白井黒子さんとその先輩の御坂美琴さん
Shirai Kuroko-san from Tokiwadai Junior High and...
her sempai, Misaka Mikoto-san.
And this is Saten Ruiko-san who is in our class.
それから私たちと同じクラスになる佐天涙子さん
よろしく
Nice to meet you.
Right, well that's that, but...
で　それはいいんだけど
Why are these boxes here?
どうしてこういうことになってるわけ
Umm... Well you see...
えっと　その　春上さんを駅まで迎えに行ってる時に
As I was going to pick up Haruue-san at the station,
引越し屋さんが到着したっていう連絡が来て
I got a call telling me that the movers had arrived...
つーか　引越し屋も少しは考えればいいのにね
Really, the movers need some brains.
とにかく　どうにかしないと
We need to do something about this.
All right, then.
仕方ありませんわね
Oh, that's a great way!
おう　その手があったか
Amazing.
すごいの
I never saw teleportation before.
<Teleport>
空間移動って初めて見たの
Of course you haven't.
そりゃそうでしょうとも
There aren't many teleporters in Academy City with powers greater than mine.
<Teleporter>
私ほどの力を持った空間移動能力者は学園都市内でもそうそうおりませんのよ
Oh...
Right now,
はいはい　さあ　ちゃちゃと片付けちゃおう
Let's start getting everything put away and cleaned.
はい
はいなの
Yes!
Phew, this should be it.
こんなところかね
Thank you very much everyone.
皆さん　ありがとうございましたなの
Don't mind it.
気にしない　気にしない
And, since we finished early,
それより　思ったより速く終わったし
let's go out!
どっか遊びに行こうか
Great idea!
賛成
It's not a "great idea".
賛成じゃありませんの
忘れましたの
Did you forget?
初春と私はこれから合同会議
Uiharu, you and I have that joint meeting right now.
What do you mean by joint?
合同って
It's between Judgement and Anti-Skill.
<Judgement>＜Antiskill＞
風紀委員と警備員のですわ
If I remember correctly, it was about the
earthquakes that have been happening recently.
何でもこのところ起きてる地震に関する話とか
地震で会議
You're having a meeting because of an earthquake?
Yeah... you're right...
はー　そうでした
Well then, she can come with Misaka-san and me.
んじゃ　御坂さんとあたしと　三人で行こうか
That's not fair!
あっ　ずるいですよ
You can join us when you're done.
終わったら合流すればいいじゃん　ねぇ
Right?
Oh, it's all right.
大丈夫ですよ
Regardless of what Saten-san is
like, Misaka-san is a kind person.
佐天さんはともかく　御坂さんは優しい人ですから
I'll be there just as soon as I'm done.
私も終わったらすぐ行きますし
あんたねぇ
Why you...
佐天さん　冗談でも
Saten-san, don't even think of flipping Haruue-san's skirt, even if is supposed to be a joke.
春上さんのスカートめくったりしないでくださいねぇ
Oh?
えっ　なんであたしがそんなことするの
Why would I do something like that?
Oh huh?
あれ　えー　だって
Eh? But...
Eh.....
さて　どこに行こうか
So then, where should we go?
Haruue-san, do you have anywhere you want to go?
春上さん　行ってみたい所はある
I don't really know much about this Academy District yet so...
まだ　この学区のことよく分からないから
I see.
ああ　そうか
Then, the usual...
じゃ　やっぱり
If we're going somewhere to get to know each other, this is the place.
お近付きの印と言えばここですよ
Come to think of it,
そういえば　佐天さんたちと初めて会った時も来たよね
we came here when we first met each other.
Does it taste good?
美味しい
Yes.
It's quite chaotic around your mouth.
口の周りにすごいクリームなってるよ
But Kuroko and Uiharu sure are busy.
しかし　黒子たちも大変ねぇ
Why do they have a joint meeting between Judgement and Anti-Skills just because of an earthquake?
<Judgement>＜Antiskill＞
なんで地震なんかで風紀委員と警備員が合同会議なんかするんだろう
It's understandable if it's some case though...
事件とかならいざ知らず
Hee Hee! I didn't say anything back there, but there's some hot rumors about that!
さっきは黙ってましたけどねぇ　実はそれに関してホットな噂が
Anti-Skill 7th Academy District Headquarters
Meeting Room 1
There's something we have found out about the earthquakes that have been happening frequently these days.
このところ頻発している地震について判明したことがある
In short, they're not earthquakes.
結論から言えば　これは地震ではない
More accurately...
正確には
Poltergeist?
<Poltergeist>
乱雑開放？
Yes!
<Poltergeist>
YES　乱雑開放
Poltergeist!
You mean...
で　あれでしょう　家具やなんかが独りでにぐらぐら揺れる
stuff like furniture starts shaking by itsel—
P波もS波も観測されないんですって
I heard that neither P-waves nor S-waves were detected.
This is a supernatural phenomenon!
これは超常現象ですよ　超常現象
An supernatural phenomenon!
などと騒ぎ立てる学生が出て来ないとも限らんから
There might be students who get strange ideas and make things complicated, so I'll clarify things before that happens.
予め　釘を刺しておく
This is not a supernatural phenomenon.
これは超常現象ではない
The cause of the Poltergeist is the simultaneous large scale occurrence of the RSPK syndrome.
<Poltergeist>
乱雑開放の原因は  RSPK症候群の同時多発じゃん
Poltergeist ---> RSPK syndrome...
RSPK syndrome is a phenomenon when an ability user temporarily loses their autonomy and is in a state of letting their ability go out of control without their conciousness.
As there are various abilities depending on the ability user, when this phenomenon happens simultaneously, their abilities fuse together and take form as a Poltergeist phenomenon.
When this Poltergeist phenomenon elevates to the level of a major phenomenon, it can be felt by others as something similar to a natural phenomenon like an earthquake.
The RSPK syndrome,
RSPK症候群の
happening simultaneously at large scale?
同時多発？
From here on, we will have Telestina-san from Multi-Active Rescue explain.
ここから先は
精神状況救助隊のテレスティーナさんから　説明してもらおうじゃん
Err... as I have been introduced,
ええ　ただいまご紹介いただきました
I am Telestina from Multi-Active Rescue.
精神状況救助隊のテレスティーナです
RSPK syndrome is a phenomenon when an ability user temporarily loses their autonomy,
RSPK症候群とは　能力者が一時的に自律を失い
and is in a state of letting their ability go
out of control without their conciousness.
自らの能力を無自覚に暴走させる状態を指します
Although the individual phenomena might vary,
個々の現象は様々ですが
when this happens simultaneously,
これが同時に起きた場合
the abilities that have gone out of control fuse together...
暴走した能力が互いに融合し合い
and take form as a Poltergeist phenomenon.
<Poltergeist>
一律に乱雑開放現象として発現するというわけです
When this Poltergeist phenomenon expands into a major phenomenon,
<Poltergeist>
さらにこの乱雑開放現象がその規模拡大した場合
it makes it difficult to distinguish this phenomenon from an earthquake.
体感的には　地震と見分けがつかない状況を呈します
This is the true form of these earthquakes.
これが今回の地震の正体ということになります
However, while we are still researching as to why the RSPK syndrome is happening simultaneously on large scale,
RSPK症候群の同時多発の原因については
目下調査中ですが
some of the students are linking this
phenomenon to stupid occultic practices.
一部の学生の間では　この現象を愚にも付かないオカルトと結びつけ
原因は別次元からの波動　特殊なプラズマ
The reason must be waves from the other realm!
It's special plasma!
You know...
ほら　統轄の理事会が秘密に行っている地下実験なんてのも
It might be some secret underground experiments the Administrative Board is doing.
Anyway,
とにかく
We can only imagine the type of
panic and damage this can cause.
それによって　集団ヒステリーなどが起き
被害が拡大することも考えられます
The reason why you Judgement members are here is because we want you to warn the students not to spread rumors like that.
<Judgement>
今回風紀委員の皆さんに集まってもらったのは
そのような噂を学生たちが面白半分で広めないよう
注意を促してもらいたいからです
They say a major one is going to come soon!
もうじきでっかいのが来るって言われてるんですよ
Huh?
Look!
Academy's Urban Legends
Destruction of The Academy City
That Day is Coming Soon!
ほら
By the way, Haruue-san, the 19th Academy District that you came from had lots of Poltergeists, right?
そういえば春上さんはいた十九学区って
<Poltergeist>
乱雑開放が多発してたんでしょう
What was it like?
どうだったの
Hey, you shouldn't play around with things like that.
こらぁ　そんなこと面白おかしく騒いじゃだめでしょう
本当に来たら大変じゃん
There'll be lots of trouble if they actually happen
It finished earlier than I expected.
思いのほか　早く終わりましたね
<Antiskill>
警備員はこの後もミーティングなんですって
It seems that Anti-Skill has another meeting after this.
Oh Konori-sempai, is anything bothering you?
固法先輩　どうかなさいまして
I've never heard about RSPK phenomenon occurring simultaneously on a large scale.
RSPK症候群の同時多発なんて　聞いたことないわ
And their countermeasures for this...
それに　今回の対応　何か引っかかるのよねぇ
Something's bothering me.
But that's what the experts are going to research now, right?
それをこれから専門家の方々が調べてくださるのでしょう
We'll get nowhere, even if we think hard about it.
今　私たちが考えても始まりませんわよ
そりゃあそうかもしれないけど
That's true but...
Oh Saten-san, where are you now?
あ　佐天さん　今どこですか
So Haruue-san, what should we do now?
さあ春上さん　次は何をやりましょうか
Oh, how about that?
あっ　あれなんてどうですか
Uiharu is so excited.
初春　張り切っちゃって
お姉様も随分と
Onee-sama, you too...
あ　いやぁ
Oh no...
I think I've seen that coin somewhere...
なんか見覚えのあるコインですね
Huh?!
Oh, Whack-a-Mole?
あっ　もぐらたたき
そっ　そうなんですが
Y-Yes but...
懐かしいですわねぇ
Haven't seen it in ages.
私　こういうのは初めてなの
I've never played this stuff before.
It's so cute how they pop up like that.
ピコピコ出てきて可愛い
Huh?
I-I see...
そっ　そっか
But you're not supposed to just look at them. You're actually supposed to hit them.
でもさ　見てるだけじゃなくて　叩いてみたら
Hit them?
叩く
That's cruel.
かわいそう
T-That's right...
そっ　そうだよね
で　ですよ　楽しみ事は人それぞれですし
That's right!
Everyone has their way of enjoying things.
One more time.
もう一回
は　春上さん　さすがに四回目は
H-Haruue-san, maybe it's too much to play it a forth time.
ねえ　みんなであれ撮らない
Shouldn't we all take a photo with that?
That?
あれ？
Here we go.
じゃあ行くよ　あい
Welcome Erii
Umm...
えっと　送信
Are you sending this image? - Yes
Send!
Sending...
Sent.
This should do it.
これでよし　はい
Here.
How should I say...
何というか　不思議な子ですわね
She's a strange girl.
Is she?
そう　可愛いじゃない
She's cute.
She reminds me of Uiharu in the old days.
何か　昔の初春を思い出しちゃった
The old days?
昔
Oh, when she first entered school...
いやあ　入学した手の頃に
Haruue-san?
春上さん
Oh watch out!
あっ　危ない
A-Are you all right, Haruue-san?
大　大丈夫ですか　春上さん
What happened?
どうしたの
That...
あれ
Academy City
Fireworks Festival
Many Events!
You mean that?
あれって？
A poster for a fireworks festival?
花火大会のポスター
Oh come to think of it, that's going on today.
あっ　そういや今日じゃないですか　それ
Hey, why not we all go together?
ねえ　みんなで行こうか
That sounds like a good plan!
いいですわね　浴衣なんか着て
We should all wear a yukata...
行きましょうか
Let's go.
乱
杂
开
放
Poltergeist
(Poltergeist)
Uncoordinated
Release
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Yes!
Academy City Fireworks Festival
Student's Night Time Leave Permission until 21:00
It's my first time wearing a Yukata.
私　浴衣着るの初めて
Same for me too.
私だってそうですよ
It might be long...?
長いかも
I'm doing research now so...
今調べてますから
Oh I found it, Haruue-san!
あっ　分かりましたよ春上さん
We're supposed to adjust the length with the band like this.
こうやって　紐で丈を調整するんです
It looks difficult.
難しいかも
L-Let's try hard!
頑張りましょう
Okay.
Umm...
えっと　まずは前を合わせて
First we get the front right...
Oh, what a cute pendant!
あっ　可愛いペンダントですね
It's kind of like... a protection charm.
お守り　みたいなものなの
A protection charm?
お守りか　いいなあ
How nice!
Right, let's get these on quickly!
さあ　着付けちゃちゃと済ませましょう
Right!
Umm... after getting the front right, the next is...
えっと　前を合わせたら次は
We pull up the collar of the Yukata about 20cm...
浴衣の襟もと20センチぐらい上に持ち上げてこうかな
Like this?
Thank you.
ありがとうなの
Huh?
You're really taking care of me.
いろいろ　お世話してくれて
Uiharu-san is a good person.
初春さんいい人
Well umm...
<Judgement>
その　私も風紀委員の端くれ
I'm part of Judgement.
That said...
とはいえ　最近は町の掃除や落とし物を探すとか　そんな程度ですが
I'm only doing things like cleaning the city and finding lost articles...
Search...?
探す？
Anyway, I'm willing to do anything I can do!
とにかく　私にできることは何でもするつもりですから
Please rely on me from now on!
ドーンと頼りにしてください
I was wondering why you called me suddenly.
で　急に呼び出すから　何かと思えば
S-Saten-san, help us!
さ　佐天さん助けてください
Here!
はい　一丁上がり
All done!
Thank you!
ありがとうなの
Amazing, Saten-san.
すごいです佐天さん
あっという間に　こんな綺麗に
You dressed us up so nicely in an instant!
Yeah yeah.
はいはい　急がないと間に合わないよ
We have to hurry or we'll be late.
はぁ　こんなことなら
I would have relied on you in the first place if I'd known things would turn out like this.
初めから佐天さんに頼めばよかったです
But, you were really trying hard.
でも　初春頑張ってるじゃん
Since it's my turn to be of support, this time.
今度は私が力になる番ですから
今度？
This time?
You know, that time when I was unable to pass the Judgement Exam,
<Judgement>
ほら　私　風紀委員の試験になかなか合格できなくて
and after that, I was unable to have confidence in other things, also.
そのせいで　他のことにも自信が持てなくなって
Oh, you were really in need, then.  I couldn't just leave you alone.
ああ　あの頃の初春って　見ててほっとけない感じだったもんね
Saten-san and the others would listen to my worries and encourage me.
そんな私を
佐天さんたちはいつも励ましてくれたり
相談に乗ったりしてくれたじゃないですか
Oh, is that so?
へえ　そうだったっけえ
Yes.
はい　そのおかげで　私　ちゃんと合格できたんですよ
Thanks to that, I was able to pass.
So, this time I thought I'd like to support Haruue-san.
だから　今度は私が　春上さんの力になれたらいいなって
Oh...
Umm...
あっ　その　私だけじゃ頼れないでしょうけど
However, it doesn't seem like I'm doing very well by myself...
Oh, no.  That's not true.
ううん　初春さんがルームメイトで本当によかったの
I'm really happy you are my roommate.
I'm relying on you.
頼りにしてるの
Oh... Yes...
はい
全く  いつの間にか　立派になっちゃってえ
My my, you grew up before I even realized it.
As your older sister, I'm so proud of you.
姉さん嬉しい
Geez... My birthday is before yours.
もう　私のほうが誕生日早いのに
そこはそれ
That's that!
What is that!
なんですか　もう
Don't move, or we'll never finish dressing.
ほらほら　動くなって　着付け終わらないでしょう
She left.
行った？
Let's go-
行きましょっと
That was close!
危なあ
This time it's okay for sure.
今度こそ大丈夫ですわね
Escape success!
脱出成功
ですわね
It is!
Geez, our dorm is probably the only place where the
curfew doesn't change despite the fireworks festival.
全く　うちの寮くらいよねえ
花火大会でも門限変わらずなんて
Onee-sama,
お姉様　そんなに雑に動いては着崩れますわよ
moving thoughtlessly like that will mess up your outfit.
はいはい
Yeah right.
You're wearing shorts even though you're wearing a yukata.
大体　せっかくの浴衣なのにまた下に短パンを穿くなんて
いいでしょ　別に　見えないんだから
Who cares.
No one will see it anyway.
見えない所に気を遣うのが乙女の嗜みですのに
It's good manners for a maiden to be considerate even about parts that can't be seen.
By the way, is Konori-sempai not coming today?
そう言えば　今日固法先輩は来ないの
<Poltergeist>
それが例の乱雑開放について調べてるんですって
Well she's researching about that Poltergeist.
It looks like something's been bothering her ever since the meeting ended.
会議が終わってからずっと何か引っかかってるみたいで
I see.
But it really is strange, that the RSPK syndrome simultaneously happens at large scale.
でも　確かに変よね
RSPK症候群が同時多発するなんて
Musashino Milk
はっ　ほんと切りがないわね
This sure is endless.
Poltergeist Photo Archives
As part of the effect of the RSPK syndrome to the enviroment, it can cause Poltergeist phenomenon. This is different from the spiritual Poltergeist phenomenon brought up in Occult magazines throughout history, and is a result of infections of weak ability around the... >>Cache
RSPK Syndrome and Polgergeist Phenomenon in Stories
The Poltergeist Phenomenon caused by the effect of weak ability among the young are reported as poltergeist stories among the young. (<- makes no sense) cache
This seems to be all of the information about it on the internet.
ネットに転がってる情報なんてこんなもんか
Oh, Misaka-san, you look wonderful.
御坂さんすごい素敵
白井さんも可愛いですね
You look cute too, Shirai-san.
勿論ですわ
Of course.
You all look cute.
初春さんたちも可愛いよ
T-Thank you.
あ　ありがとうなの
Oh, the night stalls are out!
夜店だ
Oh yes!
本当だ　結構出てるね
There's a lot of them!
Oh, it smells great!
いい匂い　堪らん
I can't stop!
Me too!
私も
お姉様　そんなに走っては
Onee-sama!
You mustn't run too much or—
Geez.
Haruue-san, we should go too.
春上さん　私たちも
Okay!
Geez, Onee-sama.
全くお姉様ったら
Leave me alone!
いいでしょう　お祭りなんだから
It's a festival.
雰囲気よ　雰囲気
What matters is the spirit.
Geez.
全く
Huh?
あれっ　何　あの車
What are those cars?
MAR　精神状況救助隊のトレーラーですわね
MAR, it's trucks for the Psychological State Rescue Team.
Is it a countermeasure against those Poltergeists?
<Poltergeist>
例の乱雑開放対策ですかね
<Poltergeist>
乱雑開放　じゃあ　あの噂マジなんだ
Poltergeist?
So that rumor is for real!
<Poltergeist>
こんな人の多い場所で　万が一乱雑開放が起きたら大変ですし
It would be a lot of trouble if a Poltergeist happens somewhere like this where there are lots of people.
それにしても　あんな警備下で花火見物だなんて
But really... How are we supposed to watch fireworks under this much security?
No spirit or atmosphere at all.
風情もへったくれもありませんの
Oh... I know a great place, then.
だったら　いい所があるんですよ
This place isn't well known.
ここ　穴場なんですよ
Oh, it's coming up again.
はっ　ほら　またあがりますわよ
It shakes your stomach doesn't it?
お腹にドーンと響きますよね
Yes it does.
うん　ドーンと来るの
It's beautiful...
綺麗なの
Musashino Milk
Maybe I should have gone...
私も行けばよかったかな
Something bothered me at first but, researching any more sites is just...
何か引っかかったんだけど　これ以上調べたって
RSPK syndrome treatment
Academy Abilty Development Clinic
Acception
Therapy and ability development
RSPK syndrome happening during ability deveoplment
Research on RSPK syndrome cause and AIM field diffusion
The relationship between the small earthquakes happening frequently and the RSPK syndrome
Huh?
AIM diffusion field?
AIM拡散力場
Tamaya!
玉屋
Kagiya!
鍵屋
It's coming again.
また来たよ
Tamaya!
玉屋
Oh?
What's the matter?
どうしたんですか
I was recalling memories.
思い出してたの
About?
何を
You see...
あのね　昔　私にも初春さんと佐天さんみたいな
Back then, people like Uiharu and Saten-san I also...
Haruue-san?
春上さん
What's wrong?
どうしたの
Huh?
I wonder what's wrong.
どうしたんだろう
春上さん
Haruue-san?
Oh hey!
ちょっと
Huh?
あれ　どこ行くんだろう　あの子たち
Where are they going?
きっと　気をきかせて私たちを二人きりにしてくれたんですの
They are probably being considerate of us and left us to ourselves!
Hey!
Now, let's flare up like the fireworks!
さあ　私たちも花火のように燃え上がりましょう
It's hot!
暑い　暑苦しい
Let's explode tonight.
今夜も　よかったね
Hey your phone is ringing.
ほら　携帯鳴ってる　もう
Geez.
Huh?
誰ですの
Who is it?
Oh.
で　何ですの　固法先輩今更
What is it now, Konori-sempai?
＜Poltergeist＞
聞いて聞いて　乱雑開放のことなんだけど
Listen to me!
It's about the Poltergeist.
Researching is fine but,
調べ物もよろしいですけど　少しは息抜きされたら
how about you take some time off sometimes?
The fireworks are beautiful you know?
花火　綺麗ですわよ
Just listen to me, will you?
いいから　聞いてってば
The cause of RSPK syndromes happening simultaneously at large scale is...
RSPK症候群の同時多発の原因は
AIM拡散力場への人為的干渉っていう可能性があるの
possibly an AIM diffusion field purposely interfered with by somebody.
An AIM diffusion field?
AIM拡散力場への
That means, the Poltergeist cases were not some coincidental accident!
<Poltergeist>
つまり　一連の乱雑開放は偶発な事故じゃなくて
Where?
どこ　どこなの
Where...?
Haruue-s-san?
春上　さん
Where is it?
どこなの
But someone is making them happen on purpose?
誰かが意図的に起こしているっていうことですの
Shirai-san?
白井さん　ちょっと白井さん
Hey Shirai-san?
This can't be...
これって
No way!
<Poltergeist>
まさか　乱雑開放
Poltergeist?
Onee-sama!
お姉様
Where are the others?
佐天さんたちは
Uiharu?
初春
Uiharu!
Saten-san, are you all right?
佐天さん大丈夫
That was close.
間一髪ね
You're not hurt, are you?
怪我はなかった
You're all right now.
もう大丈夫よ
That person is...
あの方は
Huh?
Haruue-san,
春上さん　春上さん
Haruue-san!
Haruue-san, are you all right?
春上さん　大丈夫ですか
No need to force yourself.
無理しないで
Where?
どこ
Where are you?
どこに　いるの
Haruue-san?
春上さん？
Beautiful!
きれい
Amazing!
すげえ
Did something collapse over there?
あそこ崩れたよ
Some accident, maybe?
何か事故
待
续
A Certain Scientific Railgun
To be continued
狙い定めた指先が指す
運命は絶望 それとも希望
ゆらぎの中で受信してゆく
悲しみにも負けない
勇気だけをください
大切なもの　守るため
「強さ」があると信じてる
Saving our future 一緒に
明日へのドア開いた空へ飛び立とう
とある世界の果てで
駆け抜けてくReal Force
光を放って
Next Episode
Where?
どこ　どこなの
声
音
Voice
Where are you?
右です　春上さん
Right, Haruue-san!
You went too far!
行き過ぎた　左です　左
Left!
What?
Are you smashing watermelons?
で　スイカ割りですの